[
  {
    "question": "Every Barbie needs her...?",
    "answer": "friend",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:33:11.148Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the masterpiece?",
    "answer": "princess",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:33:22.016Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Favorite frequency?",
    "answer": "voice",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:33:35.840Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Better than any...?",
    "answer": "love",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:33:47.142Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Love drive happy?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:33:55.488Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "What am I to you?",
    "answer": "love",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:34:06.432Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Every Barbie needs her...?",
    "answer": "friend",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:43:35.103Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the masterpiece?",
    "answer": "princess",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:43:51.984Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Favorite frequency?",
    "answer": "voice",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:44:08.582Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Better than any...?",
    "answer": "love",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:44:26.860Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Love drive happy?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:44:36.370Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "What am I to you?",
    "answer": "lover",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "timestamp": "2026-02-13T14:44:45.997Z"
  }
]